<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  - SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  - SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2025 Carl Schwan <carlschwan@kde.org>
 -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.systemdgenie</id>
  <provides>
    <binary>systemdgenie</binary>
  </provides>
  <name>systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">جني Systemd</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">systemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">SystemdGenie</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxsystemdGeniexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">systemdGenie</name>
  <summary>System service manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مدير خدمات النظام</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de serveis del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de serveis del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de servicios del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de services du système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מנהל שירותי מערכת</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Gerente de servicio de Systema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore dei servizi di sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სისტემური სერვისების მმართველი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Beheerder van systeemservices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik storitev sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sistem hizmeti yöneticisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Менеджер системних служб</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSystem service managerxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">系统服务管理器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>systemdGenie allows graphical management of systemd units, including user units, and provides control over logind sessions. It also includes an integrated text editor for easy modification of unit and configuration files. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يتيح لك جني Systemd إدارة وحدات systemd بشكل رسومي، بما في ذلك وحدات المستخدم، ويوفر التحكم في جلسات تسجيل الدخول. كما يتضمن محرر نصي متكامل لتعديل ملفات الوحدات والضبط بسهولة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El systemdGenie permet la gestió gràfica de les unitats del systemd, incloses les unitats d'usuari, i proporciona control sobre les sessions del «logind». També inclou un editor de text integrat que facilita la modificació dels fitxers d'unitats i de configuració.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">systemdGenie permet la gestió gràfica de les unitats de systemd, incloses les unitats d'usuari, i proporciona control sobre les sessions de «logind». També inclou un editor de text integrat que facilita la modificació dels fitxers d'unitats i de configuració.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">systemdGenie permite la gestión gráfica de unidades de systemd, incluidas las del usuario, y proporciona control sobre las sesiones de logind. También incluye un editor de texto integrado para poder modificar con facilidad unidades y archivos de configuración.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'application systemdGenie permet la gestion graphique des unités pour le processus « systemd », y compris les unités utilisateur. Elle fournit un contrôle sur les sessions de connexion avec « logind ». Elle comprend également un éditeur de texte intégré pour une modification facile des fichiers d'unité et de configuration.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">systemdGenie מאפשר ניהול חזותי של יחידות systemd, כולל יחידות משתמש ומספק שליטה בהפעלות logind. הוא כולל גם עורך טקסט מובנה לעריכה פשוטה של קובצי יחידות והגדרות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">systemdGenie permitte gerer graphicamente unitates de systemd, includente unitates de usator, e forni controlos sur sessiones de logind. Il anque include editor de texto per modificar facilmente unitates e files de configuration.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">systemdGenie permette la gestione grafica dell unità (unit) di systemd, incluse le unità utente, e fornisce il controllo sulle sessioni di logind. Include anche un editor di testo integrato per una modifica facilitata delle unità e dei file di configurazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">systemdGenie systemd-ის ერთეულების, მომხმარებლების ერთეულების ჩათვლით, გრაფიკული მართვის პროგრამაა. ის ასევე შეიცავს ჩაშენებულ ტექსტურ რედაქტორს ერთეულებისა და კონფიგურაციის ფაილების ადვილი ცვლილებისთვის.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">systemdGenie biedt grafisch beheer van systemd-eenheden, inclusief gebruikerseenheden en levert controle over logind-sessies. Het omvat ook een geïntegreerde tekstbewerker voor gemakkelijk modificeren van eenheid- en configuratiebestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">systemdGenie omogoča grafično upravljanje sistemskih enot, vključno z enoto uporabnika in zagotavlja nadzor nad sejami logind. Vključuje tudi vgrajen urejevalnik besedil za enostavno spreminjanje enot in konfiguracijskih datotek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">systemdGenie, kullanıcı birimleri de dahil olmak üzere systemd birimlerinin grafiksel yönetimine izin verir ve oturum açma oturumları üzerinde denetim sağlar. Ayrıca, birim ve yapılandırma dosyalarının kolayca değiştirilmesi için tümleşik bir metin düzenleyicisi içerir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою systemdGenie можна керувати модулями systemd у графічному режимі, зокрема модулями користувача і сеансами logind. До програми також включено текстовий редактор для спрощення внесення змін до файлів модулів і налаштувань.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxsystemdGenie allows graphical management of systemd units, including user units, and provides control over logind sessions. It also includes an integrated text editor for easy modification of unit and configuration files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">systemdGenie 支持图形化管理 systemd 单元，包括用户单元，并提供对 logind 会话的控制。它还集成了一个文本编辑器，方便对单元和配置文件进行修改。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/systemdgenie/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=systemdGenie</url>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#cdecfc</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#17a3ea</color>
  </branding>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#kde-devel:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.systemdgenie.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
</component>
